[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which American soul singer sang Living in America prior to Apollo Creeds fight with Ivan Drago in Rocky IV?", "correct_answer": "James Brown", "incorrect_answers": ["Bobby Brown", "James Black", "Marvin Gaye"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what age can grizzly bears start to mate?", "correct_answer": "4 and a half year", "incorrect_answers": ["9 years", "1 and a half year", "7 weeks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why is Luxembourg City one of the wealthiest cities in the world?", "correct_answer": "It is a banking and administrative center.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is the European center of computer and computer related companies.", "There is great mineral wealth in the area around the city.", "Rich retired people have ranked it as the most desirable place in Europe to live."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Goldfinger, which one of the following characters does not die?", "correct_answer": "Pussy Galore", "incorrect_answers": ["Tilly Masterson", "Goldfinger", "Oddjob"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Genioplasty or mentoplasty is a cosmetic surgery procedure which aims at improving the appearance of which part of the body?", "correct_answer": "Chin", "incorrect_answers": ["Buttocks", "Genitals", "Knees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The state of Indiana has strict laws against collecting and capturing box turtles from the wild.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does Brooke want Gary to take her on the movie The Break-Up?", "correct_answer": "Ballet", "incorrect_answers": ["Baseball game", "Art museum", "Opera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this game show, created by Merv Griffin in 1964, you always have to say What is...? before you say the answer.", "correct_answer": "Jeopardy!", "incorrect_answers": ["Pyramid", "Wheel of Fortune", "Family Feud"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This city in the United States claims to house the largest ball of twine which was built by millionaire J. C. Payne.", "correct_answer": "Branson, MO", "incorrect_answers": ["Lake Nebagamon, WI", "Darwin, MN", "Cawker City, KS"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dolphins are only found in the ocean.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Colin Farrell turned down the role of Hannibal King in Blade Trinity.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Peter La Fleurs dodgeball team in the movie Dodgeball celebrated their regional qualifier victory at this restaurant/bar.", "correct_answer": "The Dirty Sanchez", "incorrect_answers": ["The Brown Derby", "The Sack O Suds", "The Rusty Trombone"]}]